SARA BAENA GRANERO

C/ Félix María Samaniego nº6, Algete, Madrid 629 737 081 // 916 282 561 <u>sara_baena@hotmail.com</u>



Apr 2013 - Dec 2013

Sept 2005 - Jul 2013

DATE OF BIRTH NATIONALITY

02/05/1987 Spanish

SUMMARY

I am an Aeronautical Engineer with experience in Supply Chain and Quality in Airbus Operations, working as an international Supplier Operational Manager for all Airbus sites.

In addition, I work as private teacher for students from Secondary School to University.

ACADEMIC TRAINING

Universidad de Alcalá, Madrid

"Master in Professional Development"

Universidad Politécnica de Madrid

Aeronautical Engineering (5 years degree) – Master degree

- Airports.

WORK EXPERIENCE

AIRBUS Spain Supply Chain & Quality Manager - Standard Parts (Temporary Contract) May 2014 - Present

- Ensuring Supply Chain & Quality to meet all Airbus programs current needs.
- International Supplier Manager for all Airbus sites of major distributors (Wesco, B/E Aerospace, Pattonair, Align Aerospace), manufacturers (Trelleborg) and others.
- Approval and Quality Support of AIRBUS Standard Parts manufacturers.
- Supply Chain & Quality Support to Airbus Spain factories.
 - Quality issues: Root cause analysis, Deployment of Solution.
 - Supply Chain issues: Critical overdue deliveries and other needs.
- Standard Parts Supplier Surveillance.
- Reporting, Analysis, Problem solving, Validation of Corrective Actions.
 - On Time Deliveries
 - Rejection Rate
- Use and update of Airbus Spain SAP.
- Material Master Data administration.
- Supplier Master Data administration.
- Generation of Standard Parts forecast for supplier communication.

AIRBUS Spain Supply Chain & Quality Manager - Standard Parts (Internship)

Apr 2013 - Apr 2014

- Support for all tasks and activities listed above.

Private teacher 2006 – Currently

- Private classes of Mathematics, Physics and Spanish (Castellano).
- Students from Secondary School to University (Around 30 students).
- Success rate 80%.

Agent in a Real State, London

Sep 2010 - Dec 2010

- Salary obtained exclusively from successful rentals.
- Rental Success rate 100% (Assigned 5 rooms to be rented per week).

DECATHLON Sale of sports equipment

Oct 2008 - Feb 2009

- Stock management.
- Learning about Goods and Retail types of industries.

ADDITIONAL TRAININGS

Airbus Operations, Madrid

Jun 2014

- Training "Transfer of Work"

Instituto Tajamar, Madrid

Nov 2013

Course "Lean Logistics"

TUDelft Aerospace University, Delft (Holland)
- Course "Introduction to Air turbines"

Nov 2012

Paristech Telecom University, Paris

Mar 2012

- Course "International Management Communication"

LANGUAGES

Spanish Native
English High

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Knowledge Design of parts with Solid Edge – Intermediate

EsaComp for composed materials - Intermediate

Matlab for Systems control – Intermediate

Autocad - Intermediate

Excel, Powerpoint, Word - High